RG 062:006, Town of Beacon Falls
Connecticut State Library
Town of Beacon Falls records
1932-1994
Connecticut State Library
Beacon Falls (Conn.)
29.75 cubic feet
Administrative records, 1957-1994; Land records, 1933-1990; Tax records, 1932-1979; Court Records, 1940-1961.
RG062_006
2013-048 (except where noted)
Historical Note
The town of Beacon Falls was established in June 1871 and was taken from Bethany, Naugatuck, Oxford, and Seymour.
Scope and Content
Administrative, land, tax, and court records for the town of Beacon Falls.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Beacon Falls -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Beacon Falls -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Beacon Falls -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Beacon Falls -- Registers; Land tenure -- Connecticut -- Beacon Falls -- Registers
Places:
Beacon Falls (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
Series 1. Administrative Records, 1957-1994, billing for services, 1988-1994, Accession: 2017-028, are RESTRICTED as records may contain social security numbers and personally identifiable information. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Administrative Records, 1957-1994
  - 2016-015
    - Redevelopment petition, 1957-1959; 1 folder (Box 1)
  - 2017-028
    - Billing for services, 1976-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Billing for services, 1988-1994; 1 folder (Box 2)
      RESTRICTED
- Series 2. Land Records, 1933-1990
  - Grantor index to land records A to Z from Jan, 1, 1978 to Dec. 31, 1985 (Volume unnumbered)
  - Grantee index to land records A to Z from Jan, 1, 1978 to Dec. 31, 1985 (Volume unnumbered)
  - Grantor index to land records A to Z from Jan, 1, 1986 (Volume unnumbered)
  - Grantee index to land records A to Z from Jan, 1, 1986 (Volume unnumbered)
  - Tax liens, 1933-1975 (Volume 16)
  - Manuscript, 1936-1948 (Volume 17)
  - Warrantee and mortgage deeds, 1941-1947 (Volume 18)
  - Quit claims, 1941-1952 (Volume 19)
  - Warrantee and mortgage deeds, 1947-1950 (Volume 21)
  - Land records, 1948 April 1 - 1953 April 28 (Volume 22)
  - Warrantee, 1949 April 8 - 1958 March 31 (Volume 23)
  - Mortgage, 1952-1958 (Volume 25)
  - Manuscript, 1953-1964 (Volume 26)
  - Warrantee, 1958-1965 (Volume 27)
  - Mortgage, 1958-1964 (Volume 28)
  - Manuscript, 1964-1972 (Volume 29)
  - Mortgage, 1964-1970 (Volume 30)
  - Warrantee, 1965-1972 (Volume 31)
  - Mortgage, 1970-1972 (Volume 32)
  - Warrantee, 1971-1973 (Volume 33)
  - Manuscript, 1973-1976 (Volume 34)
  - Mortgage, 1972-1973 (Volume 35)
  - Mortgage, 1973-1975 (Volume 36)
  - Warrantee, 1973-1975 (Volume 37)
  - Mortgage, 1975-1976 (Volume 38)
  - Tax liens, 1975-1987 (Volume 39)
  - Warrantee, 1975-1977 (Volume 40)
  - Manuscript, 1976-1978 (Volume 41)
  - Mortgage, 1976-1978 (Volume 42)
  - Warrantee, 1977-1979 (Volume 43)
  - Mortgage, 1978 (Volume 44)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1978-1979 (Volume 45)
  - Warrantee, 1979-1982 (Volume 46)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1979-1980 (Volume 47)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1980-1981 (Volume 48)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1981-1982 (Volume 49)
  - Warrantee, 1982-1984 (Volume 50)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1982-1983 (Volume 51)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1983 January 26 - July 20 (Volume 52)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1983 July 20 - December 27 (Volume 53)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1983 December 28 - 1984 June 15 (Volume 54)
  - Warrantee, 1984-1985 (Volume 55)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1984 June 15 - December 7 (Volume 56)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1984 December 11 - 1985 May 20 (Volume 57)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1985 May 21 - September 17 (Volume 58)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1985 September 11 - December 31 (Volume 59)
  - Warrantee, 1986-1987 (Volume 60)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1985 December 30 - 1986 April 1 (Volume 61)
  - Mortgage and manuscript, 1986 April 22 - June 26 (Volume 62)
  - Tax liens, 1988-1990 (Volume 67)
- Series 3. Tax Records, 1932-1979
  - Old age assistance tax rate books, 1936-1945; 10 volumes (Box 1)
  - Old age assistance tax rate books, 1946-1947; 2 volumes (Box 2)
  - Rate books, 1932-1948; 17 volumes (Box 2)
  - 2016-043
    - Abstract of Real Estate Exempt from Taxation, 1950-1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Assesment lists, 1933-1979 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Series 4. Court Records, 1940-1961
  - 2017-028
    - Auditors reports - Trial Justice Court of Beacon Falls, 1959 October-1960 December (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Receipts in criminal cases, 1958 November 3-1961 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Receipts on motor vehicle cases, 1959 March 30-1961 July 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Report of collecting replacement costs, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Suspension collections, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Trial Justice Court dockets, A-C, 1940-1949, 1959-1961, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Trial Justice Court dockets, D-Z, 1940-1949, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1-4)